{
    "id": "e7ad87746d6945fca251f3255fd022d1",
    "title": "Phrasal verbs with pass exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e44f84ce6d51450db67b1f2fcf353230",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Pass",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Could you pass this brochure ....................................?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "around",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandmother passed .................................... last year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "away",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the boy who just passed ..................................... the window?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "by",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He tried to pass it ........................................ as an original painting but the curator could easily tell it was fake.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got a good job offer and I just don’t want to pass it .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She passed ........................................ at the ripe old age of ninety.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "All that belongs to him will pass ....................................... his son when he dies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "on",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I’m sorry but I think I will have to pass ................................... our invitation.",
                    "description": "Pass up and pass on are both possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was furious with the management because they passed him ...................................... in favor of a younger person.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I passed ..................................... Mangalore on my way to Calicut.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "across",
                        "over",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}